(Amy:)and a place to stay in Riyadh
for the winter.
(Sheldon:)Well, that explains those
puzzling camel race photos
(Sheldon:)on your Facebook page.
And consider this:
(Amy:)without you to make the case
for the physics department,
(Amy:)the task will fall to people
like Leonard and Rajesh.
(Sheldon:)Are you trying to scare me?
'Cause you're succeeding.
(Amy:)Well, then prepare
to be terrified.
(Amy:)If your friends
are unconvincing,
(Amy:)this year's donations
might go to,
(Amy:)say, the geology department.
Oh, dear, no! Not the dirt people!
(Amy:)Or worse-- it could go to...
(Amy:)the liberal arts.
(Sheldon:)No!
(Amy:)Millions of dollars
being showered on poets,
(Amy:)literary theorists
and students of gender studies.
(Sheldon:)Oh, the humanities!
(Leonard:)On the bright side, I don't
think President Siebert
(Leonard:)will be making us go
to any more fund-raisers.
(Howard:)It was so much easier
at my bar mitzvah.